The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Cultivation Union
This dance has 30% of the charm of a Celestial's dance.
Very good,
you shall be rewarded.
Serving the Celestial Ancestor
is already a heavenly blessing.
Disciple doesn't dare to ask for more...
Since you are so sincere,
the Ancestor
shall reward you with bliss.
Huang Yu
Celestial Ancestor
of the Cultivation Union
Middle stage Ascendant
Thank you, Celestial Ancestor...
for your blessing.
Fellow cultivator Feng.
Fellow cultivator Lin.
Today, regardless of your cultivation level...
They walk on clouds
and use jade as tiles.
This place looks like the Celestial Realm.
Why do these Celestial Seeds
feel so familiar ?
Junior Brother Wang Lin !
Quyi Chang
Heavenly Fate Sect Blue Division disciple
Late stage Soul Transformation
Junior Brother Wang Lin,
I never thought we would meet again here.
I admired your demeanor from afar
during Master's birthday banquet back then.
I am Quyi Chang.
Senior Brother, why didn't you join an army for military merit
or try to seek opportunities
instead of leisurely idling here ?
Those are just facades to fool outsiders.
This place
is where the true opportunities of Demon Spirit Land are.
This is the true door to the Great Dao !
The Celestial Ancestor is a true celestial from the Celestial Realm !
And we,
when he uses his celestial spell on us,
can have a glimpse at the Great Dao
and follow the true path of celestials !
Junior Brother must be here
to pledge allegiance to the Celestial Ancestor too, right ?
Nowadays,
even demons and ghosts dare to call themselves Celestial Ancestors...
Those who insult the Celestial Ancestor
must die !
Kill !
Your blasphemy is considered a crime !
You deserve to die without a grave !
Celestial Guardian
Cultivation Union member
Early stage Ascendant
Blasphemer...
Die !
Celestial Guardians
are the personal guards created by the Celestial Ancestor.
They're all Ascendant cultivators.
You will die without a...
They're just puppets with an empty cultivation.
They don't even have domains.
How can they be as strong as an Ascendant ?
You
still won't show yourself ?
Who are you ?
How dare you trespass into my territory ?
You already attacked me once
in Sky Demon City.
You did it again yesterday
and have provoked me.
Now you pretend to not know me ?
The assassination atempt in Sky Demon City ?
Wang Lin ?
He is Wang Lin !
Fellow cultivator Wang,
it was a misunderstanding.
Since you killed two of my Celestial Guardians,
that makes us even.
Let's...
write off our grievances !
We don't owe each other anything from now on.
What do you think ?
Celestial Ancestor is Middle stage Ascendant.
Why
are you avoiding him ?
The Celestial Guardians
are just two pieces of broken jade.
How does that make us even ?
You're going too far...
Celestial Guardians, appear
and summon the Emperor !
We pay respects to the Celestial Emperor.
We pay respects to the Celestial Emperor !
I come from the Celestial Realm !
After the Celestial Realm shattered, I descended to this place
to enlighten all living beings.
Wang Lin,
you can keep living
if you withdraw now.
If you insist on being arrogant,
celestial punishment will fall upon you !
Celestial punishment ?
Your illusion spell
is far too lacking.
The illusion was clever
but it's only a fake after all.
Your Ascendant cultivation was forcibly raised.
Just like those Celestial Guardians,
your heart lacks any comprehension of the Dao
and there's no trace of origin energy in your body.
It's time to wake up
from your fantasy.
Wang Lin...
I, a celestial, consider your cultivation hard-earned !
But you're too arrogant
and keep harassing me !
Since it's come to this...
then I'll make you a slave with my Celestial Seeds,
unable to live
and unable to beg for death !
Celestial Seed...
Begin !
As long as the Celestial Seed can make him lose his senses for a moment,
I can refine him into a Celestial Guardian with the celestial jade.
This aura...
Celestial Beast Feeds ?
Qi...
A Qilin !
Dig in.
These things have a deep connection to the Celestial Realm.
This person must have other treasures on him.
I...
What's happening to me ?
You !
You destroyed my centuries of work !
With such meager skill,
how dare you call yourself a celestial ?
You...
Don't you dare be so arrogant !
Celestial Brush
This brush
is how I enlighten all living beings !
Ignorant child,
it's time to die !
This symbol...
It's the same as the ones in the fourth fake cave !
This brush
can truly draw out the power of those golden symbols.
That look in his eyes
is exactly the same as when that Qilin saw the Celestial Beast Feeds.
Celestial Rune,
slash !
Thunder Beast,
break !
Let's go !
Celestial Beast Feeds,
Celestial jades, a Celestial Brush...
I must plunder this guy.
He used 6 different spells in 30 breaths.
This person's methods for fleeing are endless.
A Qilin...
A Thunder Beast !
What kind of monster is he !?
It's my fault... my fault...
If I weren't so greedy,
I...
I wouldn't be in such a situation !
I originally thought
that Wang Lin was just an ordinary cultivator.
That refining him into a guardian was already showing mercy.
Who would have thought he was such a monster !
Enough,
if I can survive,
abandoning my artifact doesn't matter.
You have to choose: chase me or take the brush !
Wang Lin, think carefully !
I never liked making choices.
You can count on me to handle it,
I'll definitely bring the artifact back !
Damn it, damn it, damn it !
How could he be so shameless !?
If I can escape this calamity,
I swear I will never stir up trouble again.
No !
I have one last trick !
I beg you !
Celestial Capture Net...
Celestial Capture Net
Activate !
Although I haven't mastered you yet,
I believe you will definitely help me survive this calamity !
Trap him !
Trap him !!
Trap him !!!
This is...
Again !?
Celestial Capture Net,
your previous owner
must have died because of you !
Such a good celestial artifact...
Ruonan !
Brother...
Ruonan...
Thank you, Brother Wang
for saving our lives !
H...he... he...
wouldn't dare to kill me.
W...without...
Without me
the celestial artifacts...
H...he...he...
won't be able to use a single one of them.
Master,
Little Xu has retrieved this artifact for you.
Th...this...
I'm completely exhausted.
Not bad.
This Celestial Brush is useless in your hands !
Let me go
and I'll tell you
how to draw that golden symbol.
How about it ?
No need.
Spare me, Celestial Emperor !
Have mercy, Celestial Emperor...
What's your true identity ?
Celest...
Your excellency, Celestial Emperor,
this humble one is from the Refining Feather Sect.
My name is Huang Yu.
I...I...
I accidentally entered a celestial cave years ago
and thus obtained various artifacts from the Celestial Realm.
After that... I...
I disguised myself as a celestial of the Celestial Realm.
Besides the Celestial Beast Feed and the Celestial Brush,
what else did you obtain ?
There were 2 bags of holding !
One bag contained
the Celestial Capture Net and a jade slip.
Th...The other bag
had a Divine Sense restriction.
I hadn't opened it yet
when... when...
when it was snatched away by a couple.
My daughter, Qing Shuang,
I congratulate you on becoming the Celestial King of the Rain Celestial Realm.
Father has forged a sword sheath for you out of Shuo Celestial Metal.
It can nourish the Sword Spirit within your Rain Celestial Sword.
This jade slip
has a restriction
that requires our bloodline.
You only need to use a drop of your blood to use it.
and the restriction will disappear on its own.
Only then
will its mysteries be revealed.
Judging by the tone of this jade slip,
this Qing Shuang was the ruler of the Rain Celestial Realm.
This woman had an artifact
called the Rain Celestial Sword.
Rain Celestial Sword...
Rain Celestial Realm...
There are no such things as coincidences in this world.
The woman Senior Zhou Yi fell in love with
is Qing Shuang, the daughter of Celestial Emperor Qing Lin !
Senior,
forgive me.
The first artifact is the Brush of Celestial Touch.
This brush condenses the essence of yin energy.
Father collected 12 suns to turn them into 12 symbols
that can be drawn by this brush.
In the future, when you use this brush,
you can perform myriads of transformations
to wield celestial spells.
The second is the Celestial Capture Net.
This artifact's spirit
has just awakened.
The artifact was lost to the mortal world
and used during past wars.
It is quite interesting.
It should suit your taste.
The third
needs to be paired with the Rain Celestial Sword.
It's called the Spirit Sheath.
Place the celestial sword within the sheath to strengthen it.
It can help the Sword Spirit to condense
and grow increasingly powerful.
Besides the method for refining Celestial Guardians,
there is also the Stop spell.
Although it is a low quality celestial spell,
it's profound and mysterious.
Father obtained it by chance.
This spell may be the fragment of another ancient spell.
I leave it to you to study it.
This jade slip also contains a map.
It looks to be a map of the true celestial cave.
But we don't yet know where it is...
Celestial Guardians are divided into upper, middle, and lower grades.
Even the weakest lower-grade Celestial Guardian
is comparable to Peak Late stage Ascendant.
The ones Huang Yu refined
were clearly some failed attempts.
They would be of little use in the battle against the Fire Demon Spirit.
The best thing I obtained
Stop spell
Low grade celestial spell
is this low quality celestial spell.
A true celestial spell
is something cultivators desperately seek.
If I master this Stop spell,
I might be able to turn the tide
in the battle against the Fire Demon Spirit.
In this battle...
the Fire Demon Spirit will surely be stronger than me.
Ordinary methods will be of little use.
Only by relying on spells and artifacts
will I have a slim chance.
The Scattered Devil Armor
and Ling Tianhou's sword energy
should be enough to stay alive at the beginning.
The Underworld River is powerful
but it will be hard to confront the Fire Demon Spirit head-on.
If I also use teleportation spells,
I might surprise it.
The Soul Flag and the celestial sword
if used properly
might be able to block one strike.
Although the God Slaying Chariot is powerful,
it likely isn't enough to injure the Fire Demon Spirit.
If it comes to this,
this Stop spell
might come in use.
70 years later
The Sky Demon Country and Fire Demon Country have been at war for decades.
Commander-in-Chief Lei
Fire Demon Country
Rank 300 000 Demonic Energy
(Early stage Ascendant)
Gu Yundun still dares to keep attacking with his army ?
He clearly doesn't take us seriously.
Today
our two armies
will take his Sky Demon City
and destroy his capital !
Only by swiftly capturing Sky Demon City
can we put Gu Yundun in a dilemma.
Commander-in-Chief Shui
Fire Demon Country
Rank 300 000 Demonic Energy
(Early stage Ascendant)
This barbarian tribe must also be eradicated
to avoid revealing our army's movements.
Barbarian scum,
die !
This formation is quite interesting.
Allow me to break it
and give it to the Emperor !
Go !
Stop !
What...
happened ?
The Stop spell
can only immobilize for 3 breaths.
I still haven't fully mastered this celestial spell
but I don't have time to keep studying it.
My deadline with the Demon Spirit is approaching.
It's time to set off.
Fire Demon City
Fire Demon Country
This demonic formation accumulated energy for millennia.
It's been this strong from the beginning.
We suffered heavy losses in this war
and the Ancestor orders us to continue the siege.
What are his true intentions ?
1 000 000 strands of slaughter energy...
Gather !
Leave it to me...
Break !
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.